macid.co 2017-05-13

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
     MacID
      Document last updated Sunday, 28 December 2014
                             Property of Kane Cheshire

                                            Privacy Policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and app users; this policy sets out how
we will treat your personal information.
Our website uses cookies. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies
in accordance with the terms of this policy.
(1)       What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal but anonymous information:
(a)       information about your device and about your visits to and use of this website and our app (including
your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of
visit, page views, website navigation);
(b)       information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this
website or app, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;
(c)       information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including submitting
information to us when writing a review);
(d)       information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website or app services, email
notifications and/or newsletters;
(e)       any other information that you choose to send to us;
(2)       Cookies
A cookie consists of a piece of text sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The
information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This
enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to:
keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and to handle log ins and registrations. We will use the
persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser unless a setting is activated
by you on your browser that disables the option to delete cookies when the browser is closed. Persistent
cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other
information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information
generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this
information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.
Our advertising services providers may send you cookies for the purpose of enabling the service of
advertisements based on your previous visits to our website.
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies.
For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”,
and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative
                                                        Document last updated Sunday, 28 December 2014
                                                                                     Property of Kane Cheshire

impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
(3)      Using your personal information
Personal information submitted to us via this website or app will be used for the purposes specified in this
privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website or app.
We may use your personal information to:
(a)      administer the website or app;
(b)      improve your browsing experience by personalising the website or app;
(c)      enable your use of the services available on the website or app;
(d)      send to you goods purchased via the website or app, and supply to you services purchased via the
website or app;
(e)      send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(f)      send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(g)      send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(h)      send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we
think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar
technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);
(i)      provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be
used to identify any individual user;
(j)      deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use
that information in accordance with the licence you grant to us.
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the
purpose of direct marketing.
(4)      Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors
insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose your personal information:
(a)      to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)      in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)      in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for
the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
(d)      to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are
                                                        Document last updated Sunday, 28 December 2014
                                                                                     Property of Kane Cheshire

contemplating) selling; and
(e)      to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for
disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be
reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5)      Security of your personal information
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of
your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected)
servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of
data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential and secure.
(6)      Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should
check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
Where possible we will try to notify you when any significant changes occur to this document that may
impact you.
(7)      Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such
information will be subject to:
(a)      the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00); and
(b)      the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a
photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your
current address).
We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.
You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes, by sending an email to
us. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for
marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal
information for marketing purposes.
(8)      Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third
party websites.
(9)      Updating information
                                                         Document last updated Sunday, 28 December 2014
                                                                                    Property of Kane Cheshire

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(10) Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write
to us by email to:
feedback@macid.co
(11)     Data controller
The data controller responsible in respect of the information collected on this website is Kane Cheshire (since
the provision of this document).
                                                       Document last updated Sunday, 28 December 2014
                                                                                  Property of Kane Cheshire
